Wildfires are made possible by hot, dry weather conditions as well as a supply of dead vegetation that serves as fuel.
野火的形成需要炎热干燥的天气条件以及作为燃料的枯死植被。
We may have limited control over the first factor, but we can control the second.
我们对第一个因素的控制可能有限，但我们可以控制第二个因素。
Reducing the fuel load lowers the probability of wildfires occurring, as well as the amount of damage caused.
减少燃料负荷（自然环境中可燃物质的数量）可以降低野火发生的可能性以及造成的损害程度。
This is where we can turn to goats to provide a solution.
这时我们可以求助于山羊来提供解决方案。
Goats are being used for landscape management in a number of places around the world, including Greece, Spain, Portugal, Chile and various parts of the United States.
在世界上的许多地方，包括希腊、西班牙、葡萄牙、智利和美国各地，山羊正被用于土地管理。
Goats have a very tough digestive system.
山羊的消化系统非常强悍。
Many kinds of vegetation that are toxic to other animals can be easily eaten by goats.
许多对其他动物有毒的植物，山羊都能轻松食用。
It's not just fully-grown plants that goats are able to deal with: any seeds that pass through a goat become non-viable and will not grow.
山羊能处理的不仅仅是成熟的植物：任何经过山羊消化道的种子都会失去活性，无法生长。
Human clearance teams have to worry about getting to hard-to-reach vegetation patches – goats don't.
人工清理队需要担心如何到达难以触及的植被区域——山羊则无需担心。
They are skilled mountain climbers and when standing on their hind legs, can reach up to two metres to devour shrubs and grass that humans would struggle to reach.
它们是熟练的登山者，当用后腿站立时，可以够到高达两米的灌木和草，而这些是人类难以触及的。
Because of this, using goats can reduce both the possibility of workplace accidents and the amount of money spent on fire protection measures.
因此，使用山羊可以降低工作场所事故的可能性，并减少用于消防措施的开支。
Goat herds have been found to clear some patches of land for a third of the price of human vegetation control teams.
研究发现，山羊群清理某些地块的价格仅为人工作物控制团队的三分之一。
Cost and safety aren't the only benefits.
成本和安全并非仅有的好处。
Goats are quieter than lawnmowers and people usually prefer to see goats grazing rather than litres of herbicide being sprayed on the land.
山羊比割草机更安静，人们通常更愿意看到山羊吃草，而不是看着成升的除草剂喷洒在土地上。
Children are often fascinated to see the goats at work and this provides an opportunity to educate people about preventing wildfires.
孩子们常常被工作中的山羊所吸引，这为教育人们预防野火提供了机会。